We welcome you to the magician's guild.
Could you please show me the usual list?
As you wish, Lord Sebas.
Would you tell me a little more
about this "Floating Board" spell?
Yes. Floating Board is a first tier spell
that creates a floating translucent board.
The spell is essentially used
for transporting items,
and employed in public works projects.
I see.
Then I will purchase one such magic scroll.
Thank you very much. That will be
one gold and ten silver coins, please.
Shadow Demon, please tell Solution for me
that I am looking around the city,
so I will be a little late.
Now then...
I think I will head over there today.
Shadow Demon, go!
Would you please remove your hand?
Are you in some need of assistance?
If that is the case...
Hey, old guy, where the hell
did you blow in from?
Eh?
Let me go, you old geezer!
What is this woman?
O-One of our employees!
So you did this to her with full knowledge
that she is human, did you?
And what are you going to do with her now?
Take her to the temple, because she's sick...
Then you will not have a problem
if I take her away.
L-Legally speaking, she belongs to us!
If you take her away, it would be kidnapping!
Should a proper butler
be getting himself mixed up in trouble
behind his master's back?
Fair enough.
Do you want me to help you?
I am not inclined to help a person at my feet
who can only pray for salvation to come,
like a plant, showered upon
by the rains falling from the heavens.
However, if you are someone
struggling to live...
...forget about the terror, and go to sleep.
You are now under my protection.
Like hell! I never agreed to this, did I?!
Like hell, you say?
Are you trying to say that what I said
to the likes of you was false?
Uh, no...
Then I will take her with me.
W-Wait!
Is there something else?
No!
If you take her with you,
it will spell trouble for me!
L-Look, you must know about them, right?
Eight Fingers?
The ones who control the kingdom
behind the scenes?
So, you get it? I'm begging you,
pretend you didn't see anything!
I am taking her with me.
Come on, have a heart! I'll be killed!
Saving someone who is in trouble
is common sense!
Platinum coins?! Wh-What are these for?
Take that money and
hire an adventurer or whatever.
That should be more than enough
to allow you to flee the country.
If you run as fast as you can,
it should buy you a little bit of time.
Welcome back, Lord Seba--
Lord Sebas, what is that?
I found her.
I see. I doubt that
you meant it as a gift for me.
What are you going to do with it?
What indeed? Will you begin
by healing her wounds for me?
Wounds... you say?
Could you have not left that
at the temple, then?
I could have. Imagine, me, of all people,
not realizing such a thing.
Shall I go dispose of it now?
No. I have already brought her this far.
We should think of some effective use for her.
Can I ask you to start
by assessing her physical condition?
Very well. Right away.
I will let you take it from here.
Very well.
What foolish conduct.
"Saving someone who is in trouble
is common sense."
That is what the Supreme One who created me,
Lord Touch Me, always said.
Could that be the reason why
I do the same, as well?
Might it actually be a curse?
How did it go?
Syphilis and two other venereal diseases.
Several cracked ribs, as well as fingers.
The tendons in the right arm
and left leg have been torn.
Upper and lower front teeth have been pulled.
There is also an anal fissure.
There is a possibility that the woman
is addicted to some kind of drug.
In addition, there are
multiple bruises and lacerations--
Can she be treated?
Easily.
Then please see to it.
Would it not be better to call in Lady Pestonya,
and have her use healing magic?
Solution, you are in possession
of healing scrolls, aren't you?
Please use one of those.
Lord Sebas, the scrolls were
granted to us by the Supreme Ones.
I humbly submit that they are
not to be used on the likes of humans.
Do it.
As you wish. Will rendering
the woman uninjured--or rather,
restoration of the woman's physical state
before engaging in
those activities be sufficient?
Once her treatment is complete,
can I ask you to draw her a bath
and clean her up?
I will go buy something for supper.
Lord Sebas, if you wish
to tend to her mental state,
I think it best that we call on Lord Ains.
This is not something into which
we need to bring Lord Ains.
I would have understood if Sebas
had agreed to let you be my plaything
once you were fully recovered...
Perhaps I will devour you first...
...before Lord Sebas returns.
I believe you have been completely healed.
How are you feeling?
Are you hungry?
I brought you something to eat.
Go ahead.
As long as you are here,
you are not in any kind of danger.
You have my guarantee.
When you wake up, you will still be in this bed.
Th-Thank... you... very... much...
Think nothing of it.
Now that I have taken you in,
I will ensure your safety
to the best of my ability.
Why... didn't... anyone...
...help... me... any... sooner...?
You're all right now.
I-I'm... sorry...
Please don't concern yourself.
For a man, it is an honor to offer
his breast for a woman to lean on.
But... I couldn't...
accept... such a... clean...
Here. Take it.
A handkerchief that goes unused
is a thing to be mourned.
Especially a handkerchief
that is not allowed to dry one's tears.
Please, get some rest. When you get up,
we will discuss what comes next.
What... comes next...?
You are probably uneasy
about remaining in the capital.
Is there anywhere else that you can go?
I see.
Well then, let's see...
Would you mind telling me your name?
I-I am... T-Tuare...
Tuare, you say?
Oh, yes, I have not yet
told you my name, have I?
My name is Sebas Tian.
Please feel free to call me Sebas.
Okay...
Hmm? Is something the matter?
Lord Sebas,
what are you planning
to end up doing with that woman?
You are talking about Tuare, right?
A name...?
Lord Sebas, I do not know what reasons
you had for taking that woman in,
but one receives those kinds of injuries
by being in a certain environment.
Will not those who those who did those things
be displeased that the woman is still alive?
If any problems do arise,
I will take measures to deal with them.
I would like you to wait
and see what happens for a little while.
You can do that, right, Solution?
My speed of god blade attack, God Flash.
And my absolute area of perception, Field.
If I combine these two attacks...
Blade Technique, Whistling Wind!
M-Monster...
Oh? Did you get tired?
I must say, your nail clipper
sure is dull, isn't it?
Where am I...?
You look terrible.
Gazef... Stronoff?
It was the championships of
the royal matches where we first met, right?
I barely managed to win, but from the time
I took up the sword to this day,
I've never had as close a battle as that.
Unglaus?
Brain Unglaus?
Gazef... Stronoff...
Unglaus, what the hell happened?
Tell me, are we strong?
Stronoff, we're weak. We're weak.
Our skill with the sword
is no better than trash.
We're nothing more
than humans--an inferior race.
I don't understand you.
Any warrior knows that, don't they?
Compared to ogres and giants, what are we?
There are heights to be reached.
That's why we make the effort, isn't it?
No! That's not the level I mean, Stronoff!
The real heights can't be reached,
no matter what kind of efforts we make!
The human race can never reach them.
That's the truth about those heights!
You saw something that extreme?
I did. I experienced it.
A summit that humans can never arrive at.
No, what I saw wasn't even a height.
I was so utterly lacking in ability,
it was just a game.
A farce.
Stronoff,
the strength we gain
from the sword is worthless.
In the face of true strength, it's rubbish.
I'm glad I got to see you one last time.
Now I can die.
Brain Unglaus!
Sit down,
and eat something!
Everything else comes afterward.
Everything is ready here.
Flawless.
Yeah, I know; I saw you.
I'm moving on to the next location.
I have to catch as big
a bigshot as possible, after all.
We should move to attack now, as well.
What about the other two?
Probably goofing around,
since they aren't on for this.
The hell they aren't.
They're lying in wait near the village,
in case of emergency.
Now, I'm off.
You two continue according to plan.
This won't do anything more
than buy us some time.
If we can't strike a blow somewhere
to turn things around,
then this is all futile.
Yeah, it's burning quite nicely.
I just hope the people
of the village can get away.
We're burning the plant that
the diabolical drug Black Dust is made from.
It's not just the fire; the smoke
would be bad to get caught in, too.
So, we're going to go burn
someplace other than this, right?
Yes, of course. We have to strike where we can.
Whatever else we do,
we have to prevent Black Dust
from spreading like this across the kingdom.
There are many other outposts besides this one
where they are cultivating drugs.
Eight Fingers really is a huge organization.
It sure is, Gagaran.
The largest of the underworld syndicates.
Big enough to undermine a whole nation.
We finished as planned, fiendish leader.
We left no evidence behind, fiendish boss.
Tia and Tina, did you find anything?
Nothing here.
There was no valuable information.
Ugh, so we hope for the best from Evileye.
I've returned.
Welcome back, Evileye.
Yeah. Hey, Lakyus,
catch.
What's this?
A code?
Probably.
This could be a lead on Eight Fingers.
Let's now begin the meeting.
There are several items on the agenda,
but the first thing we should
take care of is... Hilma?
Right, then.
Word is that one of your drug-growing facilities
has come under attack
by some unidentified assailants.
Yes, it has. We were attacked.
It was a village where
we had a production facility.
Hell of an expenditure.
It could put a bit of a squeeze
on our distribution.
And you have no information on who they are?
No, I don't. They were flawless.
Which is why it's not impossible
to imagine who they might be.
Hmm.
Hey...
...don't you want to bring us in?
You can't protect much with
that bunch of nobodies you put together.
No thanks. I can't afford to let you guys
know about my strategic sites.
In that case,
I'd like to take you up on that offer.
What's that, Cocco Doll?
Can you afford to pay us,
when you're on the way out?
Don't worry, Zero. The slave trade
may be legally prohibited now,
thanks to the Golden Princess,
but I have plenty of funds.
Ho, so you have something
that major going on, do you? Fine.
Oh, thank you so.
I've had a bit of a problem come up
with a woman who was
scheduled to be disposed of.
I think this will require me
to ready an excessive amount of force.
I can't very well have
that place of business going under.
Rest assured, you can count on my men.
Those of us in Six Arms
guarantee the safety of your property.